justoneeye.com 2018-06-04

# Privacy Policy justoneeye.com

At Just One Eye, we make the safety of your shopping experience our highest priority. We have implemented the latest and most comprehensive safeguards to make your transactions secure in every way. While it is necessary for us to collect certain personal information in the course of doing business, we closely guard the privacy of your personal information, from browsing history to payment method. We protect your right to privacy as set forth in this Privacy Policy, which applies to this Site but not other sites to which we link. You agree that your use of the Site constitutes your assent to this Privacy Policy.

**Privacy Policy**

By visiting our site, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. If at a later date we update this Privacy Policy to use personal information for any purposes other than those described here, we will offer you an effective way to opt out of the use of your personal information for those other purposes. Any revisions or changes to this Privacy Policy will be posted here so that you will always have the most current information on how your personable information is gathered and utilized. Your use of this Site indicates your assent to the Privacy Policy as posted.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at:

**Just One Eye, LLC**  
7000 Romaine Street  
Los Angeles, CA 90038  
[[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#90f3e5e3e4fffdf5e2f3f1e2f5d0fae5e3e4fffef5f5e9f5bef3fffd)

**Information We Gather**

We gather and store certain information from our customers to ensure that your experience with Just One Eye is as smooth and fulfilling as possible.

You provide information when you register or update your information, search, make a purchase or contact us. This can include your name, address, phone number, email address, shipping address[es] and phone number[s], credit/debit card information and additional financial information, if applicable. We may collect additional types of personal information when you choose to use certain other features of the Site, such as electing to receive text messages about upcoming promotions or events. When you choose to use these additional features, we may require you to provide additional personal information, such as a mobile phone number, and may request additional personal information such as your shopping preferences and demographics.

Please report any changes to your personal data to [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#7d0d0f140b1c1e043d17080e09121318180418531e1210) to ensure your personal data is always accurate and kept up-to-date.

We may obtain additional information about you through our Site’s technology. This includes the Internet Protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet, your browser settings, your computer’s platform and operating system, your browsing and purchase history, your location data, weblogs, cookies and other data about resources you access.

Our partner companies, including those involved with shipping, may also submit User data to us, including delivery and address information which we may use to update our records and/or communicate with you.

**How We Use Your Information**

We use personally identifiable information to give you a more enjoyable, convenient shopping experience and to help us identify and/or provide information, products or services that may be of interest to you. We use your personally identifiable information to support and enhance your use of the Site and its features, including fulfilling your order, providing customer service and otherwise supporting your use of the Site and its features. We may also track your past purchases to provide you with a personal shopping history. In addition, unless you opt out of such communications, we may notify you about new services or special promotional programs, or send you offers or information.

We do not share or disclose your personal information except as described in this Privacy Policy. Our customers’ privacy is handled with the utmost discretion. We do not provide any personally identifiable User information to any third parties, other than the following trusted JOE partners who receive information about our Users and their purchases specifically to facilitate their service to you.

  * \- Site management, maintenance and hosting
  * \- Order fulfillment
  * \- Credit card processing
  * \- Shipping
  * \- Data analysis and accounting
  * \- Credit checks and fraud protection
  * \- Customer outreach (marketing, special offers, etc.)
  * \- Customer service

**Customer Service**

From time to time, we may share your personally identifiable information in connection with strategic relationships, such as those involved in the operation of a co-branded website or web pages with a strategic partner on our Site. You should be aware that these co-branded sites may collect different or additional information. Additionally, we may provide links on our site to other websites not controlled by us. Our Privacy Policy does not apply to these third-party websites. Please consult the privacy policy of the website you are visiting.

Occasionally we may provide our postal mailing list (not email) to other companies whose products we believe may be of interest to you, based on your usage of our Site and other personally identifiable information available from our records and other sources.

We may transfer personally identifiable information in connection with a proposed or actual merger or sale (including transfers made as part of an insolvency or bankruptcy proceeding) involving all or part of our business or as part of a corporate reorganization, stock sale or other change in control.

We aggregate non-personally identifiable information to improve the Site and for business and administrative purposes. We may also use or share with third parties for any purpose aggregated data that contains no personally identifiable information.

Other than the forgoing, we only release our Users’ personal information when, at our sole discretion, we believe it is necessary to comply with the law (such as a subpoena, court order, administrative or governmental order), to apply or enforce our Terms of Use and other agreements, to protect our rights and the rights of others, to prevent harm to persons or property, to fight fraud and to reduce credit risk. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. Obviously, however, this does not include selling, renting, sharing, or otherwise disclosing personally identifiable information from customers for commercial purposes in violation of the commitments set forth in this Privacy Notice.

**Use of Cookies**

When you log into your account at JustOneEye.com, we send one or more cookies—a small file containing a string of characters—to your computer. Cookies uniquely identify your IP address and browser type, as well as, over time, your browsing and shopping preferences. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service by storing user preferences and tracking user trends, such as how people search on our site.

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some JustOneEye features and services, including adding items to your shopping bag or checking out, will not function properly if your cookies are disabled.

JustOneEye processes information collected by cookies in a collective and anonymous way, to optimize services to Users of the Site.

**How We Protect Your Information**

We are committed to protecting the information we receive from you. We follow reasonable technical and management practices to help protect the confidentiality, security and integrity of data stored on our system. While no computer system is completely secure, we believe the measures we have implemented reduce the likelihood of security problems to a level appropriate to the type of data involved.

We protect the security of any information you submit to Just One Eye with Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption technology. This allows for the secure transmission of information between your computer or other device and our servers. Only those JOE employees and third parties who need access to your information to perform their duties are allowed such access.

When processing your order, your credit/debit card information is transmitted to the appropriate company. However, when we confirm an order with you, we include only the last four digits of your credit/debit card number.

Last updated June 9, 2011

© 2012 Just One Eye, LLC. All rights reserved.
